[Gon] That's Morel's Smoky Jail.
He said he'd use it
to keep Pouf away from the King.
If it's covering
the entire third floor of the tower,
[gasps]
Hmm.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
has begun their battles
in their respective locations.
[blows landing]
[Knuckle groans]
[gasps]
[Killua] Grandpa.
That means…
that's the King.
but you wish to do so while keeping
human casualties at a minimum.
[narrator] The technique was not intended
to hurt the King in any way.
[Zeno roars]
[Gon] Killua.
Pitou is right over there.
Which is it?
[narrator] As much as Killua wanted
to ask the question,
he suppressed the urge.
There's no turning back.
[narrator] If he could only ask,
then everything would be out in the open.
Anyone with enough experience
would easily arrive at that next step.
was unable to utter a single word.
What's with all that noise?
It feels like Sir Pitou's En
disappeared again.
Well, I just got back here myself, but,
uh, it seems to me to be an enemy attack.
Seriously?
Well, I don't think
anything else could have caused this.
[Bloster] Hmm?
What happened to your wings?
Oh, uh…
I lost them during the attack earlier.
You going down?
Uh, yes.
I have orders from Sir Hagya, you see.
[rumbling]
-[Cheetu and Ikalgo gasp]
-[Bloster] It's huge!
[both] Did he say, "Sir Hagya"?
[Shaiapouf] You chose to confine me.
Do you still believe
that was the correct choice?
I wouldn't mind finding that out.
The correct choice for any good warrior.
However…
His lower vigilance
indicates an abundance of confidence.
and making the aura flow distinct.
Now I should introduce myself.
You won't tell me your name, will you?
perhaps even fatally so.
And to be quite honest with you,
I find myself feeling a bit hurt.
Hmm?
But I won't remember when I'm reborn.
[chuckling]
[scoffs]
If he wants to waste time,
that's fine by me.
I'm ready for whatever demon
or beast emerges.
[narrator] Shoot's reckless attacks
without fear for his own life
[narrator] While barely dodging
multiple attacks
that would otherwise have been lethal,
[narrator] Youpi was unable
to finish off his opponent.
Due to the series of mysterious attacks
he could not understand,
Youpi took a step back.
[Menthuthuyoupi] No matter what,
I can't let him get
any closer to the King.
[narrator] Youpi and Shoot's goals
happened to coincide.
Still, this unusual turn of events
only served to greatly torment Knuckle.
[Knuckle grunts in frustration]
Endure it. I can't strike now.
If I attack, I'd only be giving him proof
Endure it.
[narrator] Covered in blood,
[narrator] …Knuckle couldn't hold back
the tears streaming down his face.
It is time. You have accrued interest.
[Knuckle] What?
Only ten seconds have passed?
It's taking all my willpower
not to run away.
This must be some kind of joke.
You're kidding, right?
I can't take it anymore!
[roaring]
[Knuckle] Seriously?
It's only been ten seconds.
But that just might have saved me.
[Meleoron grunts]
[narrator] However,
Meleoron wasn't trying to help Knuckle.
[Knuckle] Damn it!
Oopsie!
[Knuckle] He barely scratched me,
but even so,
it was more than enough to pay off
my first full-strength attack,
plus interest.
Shoot is risking his life out there,
[yelling]
so if you wanna catch your breath,
this is the time.
[breathes deeply]
God's Accomplice, deactivate.
[Menthuthuyoupi] What is this,
and when did it get here?
There's no way I didn't notice it before.
It just suddenly appeared out of nowhere.
Was I hit by an attack?
No, that's not it.
A delayed effect?
Wait. I remember this.
Or did it fulfill
the activation condition during battle?
What is this number?
Is it a countdown, a bomb?
Can't be. The number isn't changing.
Damn it! What a pain!
-[Shoot grunts]
-[gasps]
[Menthuthuyoupi] I just need
to get rid of the source.
[Shoot] Something's coming.
[narrator] Despite his overwhelming power,
there was only one reason
Youpi was unable to defeat Shoot,
an obvious difference in talent.
[Shoot] It's fast. I can't get away.
[Menthuthuyoupi] One meat skewer
coming right up.
Huh?
[scoffs]
He hit himself to propel backwards.
who wasn't at all the strategic type
to begin with.
it was in not realizing that Shoot
was aware of this and was fine with it.
More than that…
I can still fly.
yet slowly but surely,
he was reaching his limit.
Hmm?
[gasps]
[Knuckle] Over here, you bastard!
[Meleoron] Knuckle!
[Knuckle] I'm giving him proof
that there's another enemy
he needs to worry about.
and, if we're lucky,
it might even be enough to save Shoot.
Bring it on!
[closing theme music playing]
[narrator] After he'd taken a moment
to calm down and regain his composure,
[singer singing in Japanese]
-[Gon] Right here.
-[Killua] Wait. You disappeared again.
[Gon] Perfect Plan, deactivate!
I'm always by your side.
[singer singing in Japanese]